远鉴字幕组&Orange字幕组联合制作
[Visionary] 0day-sub
喷火腚 try Arthur BoxEr Zero Ren
翻译：
橙味的六元 丛林的鱼 Edawn Shawn-LXH
Emma 复联3哭声担当 胡帅颖
翻译：
胡帅颖 Jaime_Jamie 基吉星团
没十斤公爵 青青 小白
校对：
william2568 rix 基吉星团 我问这瓜保熟么
翻译：
Jeffers Rebecca Comet 阿茴 越天然 坎坎
彩蛋制作：
基吉星团 复联3哭声担当 try 钦腾Simon
特效校对翻译与更改：钦腾Simon
这是阿斯加德
This is the Asgardian
难民船领袖号飞船
refugee vessel Statesman.
热门电影字幕欢迎关注微博 @远鉴字幕组v
远鉴字幕组招新群 483552098 诚邀您的加入
{\fad(300,0)\fs292.048\frz20\fry20\frx20\t(0.6,\fs162.25\frz0\fry0\frx0)\move(1800,778.796,975,730.12)}美国漫威电影工作室出品
我们受到了攻击
We are under assault.
重复 我们受到了攻击
I repeat, we are under assault.
美国漫威电影工作室出品
致敬漫威电影宇宙诞辰10周年
引擎受损 生命保障系统失灵
The engines are dead, life support failing.
{\fad(0,2000)\fs113.574\c&HFFFFFF&\t(0.6,\fs97.349\c&H0000FF&)\move(945,665.221,945,648.996)}美国漫威电影工作室出品
请求范围内任何船只的支援
Requesting aid from any vessel within range.
据传这段求救录音是雷神1的导演配音的
我们目前位于距阿斯加德22跳跃点的位置
We are 22 jump points out of Asgard.
我们的船员都是阿斯加德民众
Our crew is made up of Asgardian families.
士兵寥寥无几
We have very few soldiers here.
这不是战舰
This is not a warcraft.
重复 这不是战舰
I repeat, this is not a warcraft.
雷神3里出逃的阿斯加德人民全灭，已经夺得力量宝石的灭霸攻击雷神和洛
基所在的阿斯嘉德飞船 船只破损 海姆达尔重伤 锤基也无能为力
听我说 你们该感到欣喜
Hear me and rejoice.
伟大的泰坦星人拯救了你们
You have had the privilege
这是无上的光荣
of being saved by the Great Titan.
你们或许认为这是受苦
You may think this is suffering.
错
No.
这是救赎
It is salvation.
万物的天平
Universal scales tip toward balance
因你们的牺牲而平衡
because of your sacrifice.
微笑吧
Smile.
生是灭霸的人
For even in death,
死注定也与灭霸同在
you have become Children of Thanos.
我知道失败的滋味
I know what it's like to lose.
对胜利还抱有那么一点渺小之望
To feel so desperately that you're right...
却还是输了
yet to fail, nonetheless.
当恐惧
It's frightening.
使你两腿发软
Turns the legs to jelly.
我问你什么时候才到头啊
But I ask you, to what end?
就靠害怕或是逃避
Dread it, run from it...
命运还是会到来的
destiny arrives all the same.
就在这里 就在此刻间
And now, it's here.
或者我应该说
Or should I say...
我就是命运的终结者
I am.
你话太多了
You talk too much.
交出宇宙魔方
The Tesseract.
不然就要你哥哥的命
Or your brother's head.
我猜你心里应该有个数了吧
I assume you have a preference.
是的
Oh, I do.
尽管杀了吧
Kill away.
停下 我招
All right, stop!
魔方没在我们手上
We don't have the Tesseract.
它同阿斯加德一起毁灭了
It was destroyed on Asgard.
我怎么会有你这样的弟弟
You really are the worst brother.
我向你保证 哥哥
I assure you, brother...
我们会没事的
the sun will shine on us again.
你真是盲目乐观 阿斯加德人
Your optimism is misplaced, Asgardian.
有一点我得说清楚
我不是阿斯加德人
Well, for one thing, I'm not Asgardian.
还有一点...
And for another...
我们有浩克
we have a Hulk.
先让他耍两手
Let him have his fun.
请求先祖们
Allfathers...
让黑暗魔法流过我身
let the dark magic flow through me one last...
最后一次吧
time.
你那样做真愚蠢
That was a mistake.
不要
No!
你终会为此血债血偿的
You're going to die for that.
以吾卑微之躯
My humble personage...
臣服于您的伟大高贵
bows before your grandeur.
从来没有人 具有如此力量
No other being has ever had the might...
或如此的威势
nay, the nobility...
能够拿到两块宝石 而不仅仅只是一块
to wield not one, but two Infinity Stones.
整个宇宙都在您的掌握之中
The universe lies within your grasp.
还有两枚宝石在地球上
There are two more stones on Earth.
孩子们 找到并把它们带回泰坦星来
Find them, my children, and bring them to me on Titan.
我们不会让您失望的 父亲
Father, we will not fail you.
请让我插句话
If I might interject.
如果你们要去地球 最好带上一个向导
If you're going to Earth, you might want a guide.
我对那里还有点经验
I do have a bit of experience in that arena.
你真连失败都当成是经验
If you consider failure experience.
我认为经验不是水到渠成的
I consider experience experience.
灭霸大人
Almighty Thanos...
我 洛基 阿斯加德的王子
I, Loki, prince of Asgard...
奥丁之子
Odinson...
约特海姆巨人国的正统国王
the rightful king of Jotunheim...
诡计之神
god of mischief...
起誓效忠于您
do hereby pledge to you...
献上我对您不死的忠诚
my undying fidelity.
不死的
Undying?
你说话可小点心吧
You should choose your words more carefully.
你...
You...
永远不会成为...
will never be...
一个真正的神的
a god.
不
No!
这次不会再有什么假死的把戏了
No resurrections this time.
不 洛基
No. Loki.